(Penny:)What?
Secret-keeping is a complicated endeavor.
One has to be concerned...
(Sheldon:)...not only about what one says, but about
facial expressions, autonomic reflexes.
(Sheldon:)When I try to deceive...
(Sheldon:)...I myself have more nervous tics
than a Lyme disease research facility.
(Sheldon:)It's a joke.
It relies on the homonymic relationship
between tick, the bloodsucking arachnid...
(Sheldon:)...and tic, the involuntary
muscular contraction.
[CHUCKLES]
(Sheldon:)I made it up myself.
(Penny:)Okay, look, if Leonard finds out that I lied,
I will absolutely die of embarrassment.
- Physiologically impossible.
- Oh, Sheldon, please.
(Penny:)Look, I'm asking you as a friend.
(Sheldon:)You're saying that friendship
contains within it...
(Sheldon:)...an inherent obligation
to maintain confidences?
- Well, yeah.
- Interesting.
(Sheldon:)One more question.
Perhaps I should've led with this: